Hi.
My name is Helen Paul.
I am 25 years old.
I live with my father.
I am nursing...
No.. Err...
I am a B.Sc. Nursing....
I am a B.Sc. Nursing graduate.
Oops.
'Who are you, searching
for an unseen shore?'
'A lovely dove,
or the eye of a beautiful butterfly?'
'Who are you, searching
for an unseen shore?'
'A lovely dove,
or the eye of a beautiful butterfly?'
'This life... is beautiful'
'It's beautiful...
It's beautiful'
'Who are you, searching
for an unseen shore?'
'A lovely dove,
or the eye of a beautiful butterfly?'
'This life... is beautiful'
'It's beautiful...
It's beautiful'
'Solace... A solace'
'My heart is waiting for it'
Tea is in the table.
It's 'on', not 'in', right?
Would anyone keep tea 'in'?
Tea is on the table.
Okay.
Tea is on the table. - Learn it by
saying without looking at the book.
Yeah!
Since you didn't send me to an English
Medium school, expect only this much!
Yeah right!
Do you know about KR Narayanan?
KR Narayanan studied in a Govt. school,
& became India's President, right?
I've heard that!
So you know that.
Stop giggling and finish your bath.
It's time for me to leave.
So Papa, 'Tea is on the table'.
Okay?
Papa...
- What is it?
Are you smoking?
You flushed the cigarette, right?
Cigarette, it seems!
I just flushed, like I do usually.
Then why are you
still sitting there?
Sigh! This girl!!
Don't try to cover up.
What will happen if you smoke?
Papa!
Smoking increases?
Increases blood pleasure..
Then...
Not pleasure.
Pressure.
Can't even say it properly.
Say the rest.
... and can lead to heart
attack and cancer.
That means?
I know!
- Then tell me.
I'll be dead!
So it's not because
you don't know that.
Going to the bathroom with the
phone has become a habit now?
No...
I got a great prayer
of Mother Mary.
If I send it to 25 people,
our wishes would come true.
I sent it to 20 people.
Just 5 more people left.
- Oh Papa! - Let me try it, dear.
I'll give you 5
minutes to get ready.
Buying that phone for
him was a mistake.
Get ready quickly!
Hi Chechi.
- Hi.
Sumechi...
Seems like you got
your chit fund?
It looks great.
Okay. Shall I go?
Raghavetta, good morning.
- Good morning.
Wow! Hogging nicely, huh?
No, dear.
I'm done.
Don't you have class today?
- No. I have study leave.
Dear...
Tell me if any of mother's
medicines have run out.
I will.
Very nice.
Your Arthritis isn't getting cured,
because you keep walking barefoot.
You never obey what I say.
You could have come
after 5 minutes.
When it's 9 o'clock, my heart
starts beating faster.
You gave birth to 5 children, but
you're still scared of a needle?
It will be done now.
Slowly.
- I'll do it slowly.
It's done.
Okay.
Hey!
Come and sit here.
No. I don't have time to sit.
What's the matter?
You're running around so much!
Razel tablets are over, okay?
Stop beating around the bush.
Paul had come here yesterday.
Hey! If you've taken up any task
from Papa, don't try it with me.
He doesn't like you
going to Canada at all.
Do I really wish to live
in some unknown country?
That house is under
my name just for now.
The bank keeps calling to ask whether
they can make it under their name.
Then why don't you
do this job here?
Even after doing so many protests,
nurses are still paid peanuts here.
That won't solve our problem.
And yeah, I have some other
intentions in going there, as well.
What?
In Canada, there's a huge demand for
people above 70's like you, Devammal.
Let me see if I can set you up with a
handsome foreigner after getting there.
He was lazing around for so long.
Once he's ready, he'll start hurrying.
'Helen!', he'll call now.
Helen!
- The call has come.
Shall I leave?
- Okay.
Hey!
- What?
Don't look for grumpy old men.
Someone around 50-60 years old.
- Look at you!
Look at your smile! Let me see if
you'd be around till next Christmas!
Okay.
Bye.
Come home in the evening.
We'll have a drink.
Not today. I'll come tomorrow.
I'll be late today.
There's auditing... - Raghavetta,
Papa's quota for this month is over.
Not me.
It was your Papa!
Great! Me?
- Whoever it is!
There's no time for
your make-up now!
I'm going to get my bag.
Wipe off that mortar
from your neck first.
It's not mortar.
It's Cuticura (talcum powder).
Are you coming or not?
Let's go.
Switched off the gas cylinder?
- Yes.
No. Wait.
I get confused when you ask!
As soon as I said...
Hey!
- I'll be right back.
[mumbling]
Papa, had you gone to
Raghavettan's house yesterday?
What?
Raghavettan's house?
- No.
I didn't go there!
I'll punch you if you lie to me.
Neighbours would keep going to
each other's houses. So what?
Counting this, it's the sixth
person to speak for you, to me.
Mr. Paul, shall I ask you something?
For roaming all around town to
grab a few insurance policies,
how much do you
get in a month?
Why do you want to know?
Why am I going for this part-time job,
when I have no time after the IELTS class?
To get rid of your boredom.
Why else?
Papa!
What do you want now?
You want to go to Canada.
Go!
Leaving your Papa alone here,
go to Canada, America, wherever.
Problem solved?
Long back when you went to the Middle East,
Mummy & me were all alone, right?
Did I go there to have fun?
Staying in the damn hot sun there, I
lost all my fairness. Do you know that?
That's what I also said.
What?
That I'm not going
there to have fun.
Yeah right! As if I need
you to make money for me!
Stop here.
Get down.
How much, sir?
- For 110 Rupees.
Who's on the phone?
It's Shahina, Papa.
Why don't you pick up then?
It's a petrol bunk, right?
Why can't you be friends
with our people?
By our people, you mean?
We're first class pure Christians.
Which era are you
living in, Papa?
Here.
Okay, sir.
Papa, don't tell me that you didn't
see the missed call like yesterday.
Your phone is not on
silent mode, is it?
When you see the missed call, have
the 'before food' medicine at noon.
I know!
I should have the rest of the medicines
after food. That's all, right?
Balance.
Okay, sir.
When you go to Canada...
this will be difficult. When it's
night there, it will be day here.
You know, right?
I'll set an alarm to wake up, okay?
- Okay.
There are many children who
leave saying all this, dear.
Let's wait and see.
- Are you saying that I'm like that?
I just said generally.
What?
I was just speaking generally.
Oh God!
Shall I go?
Okay then.
- Hey!
Come here.
- What?
How's that friend
of yours, Shahina?
Can you convince her
to get a policy?
Oh no! Shahina is not among
our people, right Papa?
You can convince many true
Christians to get policies, right?
Go! Go!
- Okay.
Did you get the date?
No! I'm taking it slowly.
I failed twice. I can't repeat it.
Everything else is okay. But sitting in
front of those idiots for 'Speaking'...
I don't understand a
word of what they say.
Just watch English movies for that.
My family won't let me watch them,
since they have adult content.
Great! Hey! Let me go.
It's time for my bus.
Bye.
Madam, please have a
look here and go!
Hello!
I can drop you in the evening!
Jins, why can't you check this stock?
We have to supply the
stock to 4 stores!
What will I say,
when they call me?
Sir, we'll get it
ready from tomorrow.
We can get the stock
What did you say now?
From tomorrow...
Don't even utter the
word 'tomorrow'.
Understood?
Tomorrow, it seems.
Wipe it!
- I'm wiping, sir.
Hi.
Wait.
- What happened?
Oops.
Sorry sir!
Are you playing billiards here?
No, sir.
- Do what I said!
Do it.
You guys think you can fool me.
- No, sir.
Not a fly would move here,
without this Jayashankar's knowledge.
Do your work, man!
Hi. Your order, sir?
'Who are you, searching
for an unseen shore?'
'A lovely dove,
or the eye of a beautiful butterfly?'
'Who are you, searching
for an unseen shore?'
Why don't you guys learn?
You should learn how to
deal with customers.
I will learn, sir.
- Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
Is your chicken in-house,
or is it from outside?
Watch!
Sir, our poultry farm
is at Thodupuzha.
Then coming in small small
auto rickshaws and trucks.
Our chicken is...
soft, gentle...
... and crispy too!
That's not what I asked.
Isn't this why I told you for so long, that
you should learn to deal with customers?
Sir, he is the right person.
Is your chicken in-house,
or is it from outside?
What?
Sir, is there a problem?
I just wanted to ask if the chicken
is in-house or if it's from outside.
Sir, all the chicken are
from own poultry farm.
We don't use anything
from outside.
Okay.
That's good.
Sir, your bill?
Thank you.
Your English is so good.
Thank you, sir.
'This life... is beautiful'
'It's beautiful...
It's beautiful'
'This life... is beautiful'
'It's beautiful...
It's beautiful'
Hello, good evening.
Chicken Hub!
Can I take your order, please?
Helen, forgive me.
Forgive me this one time. Please.
Sorry sir.
Out of stock.
Is it Azhar?
What's the problem this time?
Chechi, people should have some
kind of responsibility, right?
He had a job interview yesterday also,
and he want to play ball instead.
And he lied to me
that he went for it.
My dear...
Didn't you say that you saw
him for the first time,
when he was brought to the hospital
with injuries after a fight?
I have no idea how you fell
in love with him then!
Chechi, from my experience,
when someone gets a
strong injection,
if he cries 'Mummy' instead of 'Oh no!',
he should be decent.
You are crazy, girl.
We just had a small fight now.
We will solve it soon.
After all, who is perfect?
Don't you and Prakashettan fight?
You're the one spoiling him!
You'll learn when
you get married!
See, when I spoke
about Prakashettan...
People are coming.
Get the bill.
Hi Ma'am. Can I take your order?
One Zinger burger.
Sir...
Doesn't this have any butter?
- Sorry sir. We're low on butter.
But the bill isn't low, right?
Sorry sir.
Have you come to eat this,
or watch the movie?
I had stopped watching
English movies with you.
But this one's 3D, right?
I really wanted to watch 'My Dear
Kuttichathan' when I was young.
I was bedridden,
after falling from a tree then.
It had released again some years back,
right? Why didn't you watch then?
Great! That was when your
mother was in the hospital.
What would people say if I watch a movie
wearing 3D glasses in between that?
So your problem is what people would say,
and not watching the movie, huh?
Not just that. With the hospital expenses,
I was really tight then.
Hey! I can't see anything,
after wearing this.
Wear the glasses only
when the movie starts.
Then why don't they give it then?
Hey! Explain the dialogues which
I can't understand, okay?
There would be
subtitles below.
Get in.
By the time I read that,
the visuals would go off.
Sorry.
This place isn't cool enough.
- Hello!
Who is it, with you?
What?
- Well...
I was asking if
you were her dad.
Sit there, dear.
What all does he want to know?
I'm not her dad.
I'm her elder son.
You can't forgive me, huh?
Shall I tell Papa?
Azhar, what are you doing here?
Then what else should I do?
I can't forgive you.
Get lost.
You haven't picked up the phone for 3 days.
- The movie is starting.
This man!!
Azhar, please go.
- I won't go.
Let Papa know who
your Shahina is.
If you don't forgive me,
I'll fall at your feet now.
Don't fall at my feet.
Papa is here.
Then say that
you've forgiven me.
Okay. I forgive you.
Really?
Yes. Really.
Shall I go then?
Yeah! Go!
What now?
- Well...
Say 'I love you' once.
Get lost!
Hey! What did he say now?
Just said 'I love you', sir.
Between two dolls?
This is what.
These English movies don't have any logic!
Telugu is the best for that!
'O golden star,
can you spread your golden sheen?'
'O sky, will you look at the
mirror to see her beauty?'
Helen!
Get me that remote!
What?
- Switch on that fan!
Helen!
Just scratch my back for me!
Your back, huh?
'O golden star,
can you spread your golden sheen?'
'O sky, will you look at the mirror?'
Always on the phone?
There was a WhatsApp
message from NASA,
that cosmic rays would be passing
through the sky, tonight after 2 AM.
You shouldn't be so careless about it.
Go to sleep!
'Without taking away the smile on her
face and the scent on her cheeks,
will you go by, O breeze?'
'Can you sing lullabies for her,
in a different tune, every day?'
'O girl who casts a net with
colours and a magical mind'
'Love showers within you,
like an endless rain, O star'
'O beauty'
'O golden star,
can you spread your golden sheen?'
'O sky...'
Smile, Papa!
'You should shine endlessly,
in the flame of smiles'
'Dreams should spread,
like sprouting flowers'
'O golden star,
can you spread your golden sheen?'
'O sky, will you look at the
mirror to see her beauty?'
Hey 'Light that never goes out'!
Get lost!
Mess with your own kind!
Your daughter is coming.
Littu, dear.
How are you doing?
Great, uncle.
- Good.
Hey! Seems like he's
really happy today.
He's hiding something.
Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Uncle, I'm leaving.
'The way you look at me,
oh my God'
What to say, right?
'The way you look at me,
oh my God'
What?
Come.
What is this?
Well...
[mumbling]
That...
I...
Place your hand on it.
Why?
Place your hand, I say.
Now give me all the
cigarettes you have.
That's all? Where are you taking your hand?
Place it here.
That's all?
There's more.
- What?
- There's more? Go get it.
What is this, Papa?
A gangster's den?
I have only seen you running
around for mom's treatment
during your entire young age.
But mom didn't bring
it upon herself.
All I remember is the hospital,
and the smell of so many medicines.
After some time, I would
also reach that age of yours.
If you smoke so much,
and get some disease,
you want me to run around
like you did then?
Open your mouth.
Papa...
I'm going to Canada and trying
to get a good job there,
not because I like to
stay away from you.
Shouldn't we live peacefully after
clearing all our debts, Papa?
Stand by me, please.
Hey...
Can I smoke a cigarette,
one last time?
Quitting smoking
is not a problem.
But still, let me
ask you something.
Ask me.
Every day...
after dinner...
.. one cigarette?
Is there a problem?
You will never learn, huh?
If you say no, it's fine.
But it's...
Dude, come fast.
You Christians hog on
chicken and beef, right?
And you still can't?
Look at me, being so cool,
despite being a pure vegetarian.
Yeah right.
Look at you!
Coldness doesn't differentiate
between Hindu or Christian.
It's a total frozen feeling.
Hey! One second.
Hello!
- Hello!
Are you leaving?
Be cool and deal with it.
- Hello?
If I be cool anymore, I'll turn into ice.
- One second.
Can you hear me now?
- Yes.
Why couldn't I reach you earlier?
I was busy here.
I will also say
this from tomorrow.
Huh?
Got it?
Got it.
But the posting is in Chennai.
I have to leave tomorrow itself.
Is it?
- Well...
If you're sad, I won't go.
I'm not sad at all.
I will leave early today.
Why?
Don't you want to meet?
I want to...
Any problem?
No problem.
Come and pick me up then.
Okay. I will come.
- Bye.
Dude, let's go.
Aren't you coming?
- You drive. I'll come.
Dude, do you have any perfume?
What will you do after
going back home early?
Helen, you know, right?
It's been only six months
since I got married.
Do I go home early from here,
at least one day?
I leave only after all of you leave,
and after closing this shop.
Do I take leave on any Sunday?
No.
You know why?
Commitment towards Chicken Hub.
My commitment towards the Hub.
None of you have that.
Do whatever you want.
Go.
- Thank you, sir. See you tomorrow.
Go! Go!
What happened?
If I have to leave 2 hours early, I have
to hear his speech for half an hour.
Well, how is he going tomorrow?
By bus, he said.
Do one thing.
You take him to the bus stop yourself.
Otherwise, he'll go
to play from there.
No, Chechi.
I think he has become more sensible now.
Chechi, shall I leave?
Or I'll get late.
- Okay.
Hey!
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I know.
Hey! They said that jobs in
Chennai pay really well.
If you join some hospital there,
then Canada...
I needn't go to Canada, right?
- Yes.
I will go.
So that's your decision?
Then I'll tell my mom,
and look for some other girl.
Pray really well.
Will you marry some other girl?
- Yes, I will.
I will marry.
- For sure? - Yes.
Why? - Then I'll go to Canada,
only after your wedding.
What? - I'm going to Canada
only after attending your wedding.
Even if I have to barge in,
I will come.
Go!
Stop! Stop!
Stop there.
Stop there, ahead.
Sir, please do something.
Please do what?
- Where's your helmet, son?
I didn't take it, sir.
Then get down.
Get down.
Come.
Will it be a problem?
- No.
You stay there, dear.
Rs. 100 won't do.
- I don't have money, sir.
Sir, he doesn't have a helmet.
Where are you going
in the night?
To drop her home...
Who's that?
If it's a case you can't
talk about, you needn't.
You were roaming at night
without a helmet, right?
Pay the petty case fine and go.
You tell me.
200 Rupees, sir...
If you drink & drive,
the law is different.
This is all I have, sir.
- That's all?
That's all, sir.
I swear.
Nothing more, sir.
- Then go.
Shall I get the key, sir?
- Yes.
Hop on, quickly.
Stop staring and hop on.
Let's go.
Hop on!
- Hey!
Wait.
Azhar, I'm getting late.
Hey! Get that thing.
- Sir.
Blow into it.
It struck!
Dear, do you want to blow?
If you drink and ride pillion,
there's no law to catch you.
But I was just asking...
Do the necessary things...
Where is your house?
Changambuzha Nagar.
Where?
- Changambuzha Nagar.
Tell him your dad's number.
- Sir...
No need, sir.
Please.
Aren't we going, man?
If we leave this girl
alone at midnight,
and something happens to her,
wouldn't I be blamed?
- Sir, please. Don't charge a case.
Shut up!
Give him the number.
Sir, should we create a
problem, informing her family?
It's very close-by, right?
Why don't we send her
in an auto rickshaw?
If she can roam around with
guys like him at midnight,
she won't have a problem in getting
into this police jeep with us too.
There's a lady constable, right?
Let her family know it, man!
Aren't you done?
- Yes, sir.
Get in.
Give me your license.
Here, sir.
Isn't it this address?
Yes, sir.
- Then say it.
Azhar Mohammed.
Sir, tea.
Give a tea to that stoner guy too.
Tell me, son.
- Ameera Manzil...
Ashoka Road...
No tea for me, sir?
Do you want one?
No!!
Is your house close
to that school?
No, sir.
Just before Elamakkara.
What does your father do?
My father is no more.
Who all are at home?
- Me and mom.
Tell me your number.
It's 854...
Son... Tell me the rest of the number.
Shouldn't I write this?
- 854...
77...
26...
Sir, I was called here.
Who are you?
- My daughter...
Come!
Sir...
That girl's father has come.
Ask him to come.
Please come.
Sir, my daughter...
Hey! There's no problem.
Please sit.
Dear, come here.
Come!
Sit down, dear.
Do you know him?
No, sir.
So it's without the
family's knowledge!
She was with him.
Actually, we needn't
interfere in this.
But we are responsible about
the girls in our city.
Why?
Isn't that right?
Not me.
It's him.
That's the mad guy, sir.
Let him lie there.
So what I'm saying is that...
like advising college kids...
we don't have to advise them.
Because they are
working people...
Right?
But still, listen dear...
When you jump into such
shady relationships,
minimum, it should be with someone
with a sense of responsibility.
Because you have to live with guys
like him in the future, right?
Well.. If that's the case...
So I just called you, so that the
family is aware of all this.
Okay.
- There's no other problem.
Okay then.
Okay, sir.
- Okay.
Papa...
Sir, tickets are available
from next month 20th onwards.
Since it's the season, fares are
slightly higher. You're flexible, right?
She wants to leave immediately.
Don't delay it any further.
Book for the very next day available.
- Okay.
Anything else?
- No.
Ma'am...
Ma'am, please...
Papa...
Don't you check the list now?
No, sir. The inventory list had come.
- It had come. Then?
What happened?
Were you in charge of checking
the fresh stock yesterday?
Yes, it was me and Shyam.
A rat entered the
stock and ruined it.
He is looking for you.
Come, come.
When an inspection happens,
you just have to smile like this.
Who has to hear a mouthful from those guys?
Me!
When a stock comes,
you have to check it.
I've told this to you
all, a hundred times!
Not just one or two...
5-6 boxes were ruined!
It's worth around 3000 Rupees!
Will your dad bring that money?
Why are you staring at me?
Huh?
Why?
I don't see this discomfort
while you ask for time off!
If something like this
happens ever again...
this is not how I would talk!
Understood?
They all come dressed up
in the morning itself!
Come.
Come!
Though the counter is very busy,
never miss this!
Rice, beans and what not!
Mix it and stuff it in!
I'll stand.
Thank you.
- Okay.
Sir, your order?
- Helen...
I want to talk to you.
Come outside.
Sir, your order?
Helen, I need to talk to you.
Come out, I say.
Sir, customers are waiting.
Can I get your order please?
Helen, please. I'm leaving today.
That's why I'm saying this..
This can't happen here...
Can't you see customers waiting?
- Sorry, sir.
Keep such games outside the shop.
Her damn...
- Sorry, sir.
Hey!
One Coke & french fries....
If you want to say something to your
staff, do it after us customers leave.
Give it.
One mega pack, and one Pepsi.
Please wait for five minutes.
- Okay, sure.
One zinger burger, one Pepsi.
Is that all, sir?
- Yes.
If he had any kind of responsibility,
would he do this?
Don't sit like this.
Forget it.
You are all set to go now.
Don't think about
anything else now.
Dear, it's 7 PM.
If I don't leave now, Prakashettan's
mom would create trouble. I'm leaving.
How are you going?
I'll take an auto rickshaw.
- Okay.
Chechi...
It's late.
Aren't you leaving?
- Yes.
I'm going then.
See you tomorrow.
Azhar...
Hey! Your shirt...
Where did you reach?
Chechi, I'm at the shop.
At the shop?
It's 11.45 PM.
What are you doing there?
Chechi, Papa hasn't spoken
a word to me till now.
I don't know how to face him.
What's wrong in facing him?
He's your Papa, right?
I don't feel like
going home, Chechi.
Hey girl! Don't speak nonsense.
Get going soon.
Chechi, how will I face Papa?
Hey! There won't be any problem.
Everything will be all right.
You go home first.
What can I do after going home?
She's not even letting
me touch her.
If I go close, she would say 'tomorrow'.
Let's make it tomorrow.
I get furious when I
hear 'tomorrow' now.
That perfume you gave?
I used that too.
Sir...
- She doesn't like its smell.
Keep it inside & go!
It's the chicken.
Not to you.
I said it here.
Shouldn't we buy soda?
I've arranged it from here.
Just walk.
Get going!
Hey! Hey!
- Oops! Caught!
What is it?
Nothing.
We were leaving.
Will someone else keep this?
I'll keep it, sir.
- Keep it in the freezer.
Just lazing around...
I thought he must have seen
me flicking the Pepsi.
I said it here.
Come fast.
Helen, can you please keep
these boxes in the freezer?
Otherwise, that monster won't let us go.
Please.
It's time for me to leave.
Helen, please.
We have an urgent plan. That's why.
Please..
- To booze, right?
Oh no! Who said that?
No one said that.
Nothing like that. Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
- What is this? - No. I'll keep this.
Come! Come!
Chechi, I've kept it here.
- Come, dude.
Oops. One second.
I didn't punch out.
Great! Would've lost
the salary now.
Come.
- Let's go!
We've kept it, sir.
I'm supposed to be a
terror at Chicken Hub.
Only I know my situation at home!
Her mom is crazy, dude.
That's what!
She says that it is
some problem of mine.
They've asked for some
motility test now.
To check my count, dude.
Let her make her
dad do that first.
Dude, I'll tell you something.
I can't wait any longer.
I have my own ways.
I'll do something soon!
Huh?
What problem?
There won't be any problem!
I will do it!
Dude, what stuff did you buy?
Huh?
Vodka?
Dude, you don't know!
They've left it open and gone!
Dude, one second.
Let me lock it.
Didn't you tell me that
you had some idea?
I was punching out.
One second.
Dude, I'm closing the shop.
I'll call you now.
Sir?
Sir!!
I'm done, dude.
I'm getting into the left.
The signal might get cut.
Sir!!
Dude, the mall is closed.
We'll buy that tomorrow.
I locked it and came out.
Sir, please!
Well.. Hasn't Helen reached home yet?
Well...
Her timings keep shifting, right?
She will come now.
Sir, any luggage to keep there?
Any luggage?
No.
- We're about to start.
Excuse me.
- No. Haven't started yet. One second.
I will reach there by evening.
Prakashetta, can't you
hear the phone ringing?
Hello uncle?
She hasn't reached yet?
I left a little early today, uncle.
One second. I'll call those
guys and call you back, uncle.
Hello?
What is it, Chechi?
When I left,
she was sitting in the pantry area.
Chechi, try calling Jins or Amal.
They would know.
Don't you want Pepsi?
Yes, Chechi.
Chechi, we left early.
Helen left after that.
Try calling sir.
I'll call sir, then.
Okay.
Tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow!
What is it, Littu?
Helen punched out & left.
I also left.
People don't decide things
after asking me, right?
And lame excuses after that!
Sir, do you know anything?
I don't know.
I left from the shop.
You find out where
else she went!
Hello uncle!
They're saying that
she left from there.
Is that so?
Okay.
Let me see.
Hello!
Is anybody there?
Please!
Help!
No. I came for a movie with him.
No. We've left.
Papa, I can hear a sound here.
Dude, one minute.
I'll call you.
Come.
There's no sound.
Papa!
Papa, leave it.
So you found out that the girl
left from the mall, right?
Yes, sir.
She left for her
house from there.
That's a problem.
You know Surabhi
textiles, near the mall?
Our station limit
is only till there.
Since this girl left the
mall and left for the house,
it will be under North station's limit.
- But sir...
I will explain.
If we charge the case in a
different station limit,
there will be problems
for both you and us.
Moreover, in these places you mentioned,
they will be able to investigate better.
So...
Why don't you do that?
That would be better.
Okay.
Hey!
No problem, right?
There are certain problems for that.
That's why.
Okay.
Helen...
Paul.
- Namaste, sir.
Yesterday's...
- What's the case?
You?
He's coming daily or what?
- Sir, his daughter is missing.
Who?
Yesterday's...?
You must have beaten her
up after going home, huh?
No, sir!
Did you enquire with
everyone you know?
I enquired everywhere
where she would go.
I was told that she hasn't
reached any of those places.
At what time does she
come home usually?
Around 12 AM...
She comes home at that time?
Her work gets over
only by then, sir.
What's her work?
At Grand Mall, in Chicken Hub.
Well...
Did you enquire with that
boy we saw yesterday?
No, sir...
She doesn't have anything to
do with him, like you think.
Don't have too much
self-confidence.
You know how kids are these days!
Get him that guy's details.
Go.
Enquire with him first.
If you don't find her even then,
we'll see then.
Sir, my complaint?
- Hey! First enquire with him!
Then whatever it is,
we'll see later.
Okay. Go!
Unnecessary troubles!
What happened?
Can't get through.
It's switched off.
Paul, we have his address, right?
Why don't we go to his
house and enquire?
But Raghavetta...
She won't do that...
- She wouldn't have done so..
But what if we get some
information about her?
Shall we go?
Who are you?
What is it?
We wanted to meet Azhar.
We tried calling him so many times.
Can't get through.
He is not here.
He got a job and went to Chennai.
When did he leave?
By tonight's bus.
Did he say anything
in particular?
He didn't say anything.
What is it?
Is there any problem?
No.
There's no problem.
In case he calls...
ask him to call on this number,
without fail.
Whenever he calls, don't forget
to give him this number. - Okay.
Whose name should I tell him?
- Just say Paul came.
Azhar knows.
Okay then.
Shall we go?
It's nothing!
It's a slight dislocation.
Nothing to worry.
It's done, okay?
Okay?
Over here.
Did you get any information?
- No.
We can't get through
to that Azhar guy too.
She told me that he got a job
in Chennai and was going there.
Paul, shall we go to the
police station once again?
Who is it?
It's from that guy's number.
- Pick up.
Hello? Hello?
Oops. The call got disconnected.
Call back on that number.
Where is my daughter?
I don't know.
I don't know!
Leave him, uncle.
- Tell me!
Where is my daughter?
- I don't know!
Leave him.
- Where is she?
Listen to me.
Move.
- Don't let him go!
Come here.
- He knows!
He knows where my daughter is.
Leave me!
How many times do I tell you
that I don't know where she is!
Doesn't she leave
with you usually?
I left early today.
Jins said that those guys left first.
When I called the manager, he said
that she has punched out & left.
Where has this girl gone?
Littu...!!
- Yes?
Dear, we don't have
any time to waste.
I don't believe what
he's saying, at all.
We'll go to the police station with him,
immediately.
Paul!
Let's go to the station.
Hey!
Come & get into the car.
Start the car.
Sir...
What is it?
Sir, those people who came earlier?
That missing case?
Sir, they have brought him.
But the girl isn't with him.
I will take an hour to reach there.
Ask them to wait.
Sir, one hour is a long time, right?
Just do what I say!
Sir...
Please give me the phone.
I'll talk to him.
Sir, how can you speak
so irresponsibly?
It's past 2 AM now.
Why are you making us run
around here and there?
Hey! Hey!
Shouting at others, without
raising your child well?
I will come after one hour,
and I will enquire if I feel like it!
You heard me?
Hang up!
He is a peculiar character.
Go directly to the houses
you called earlier, and enquire.
All those problems
happened yesterday, right?
What if she stayed
away because of that?
Her friends might not say the truth
if you speak over the phone.
Sir, she won't go like that...
- You don't speak a word!
You are the one who caused
all these problems!
Paul...
Come, let's find out.
Walk...
Get into the car.
Uncle, when I called Helen in the morning,
I felt that she was upset.
She didn't tell me why,
when I asked.
I am still with them.
That right turn
from the junction?
No. Not there.
- She didn't call after that?
No. She didn't call after that.
Here.
Your...
I don't know what your intention is.
We enquired everywhere
she could have gone.
Now...
I...
I'm asking because I don't
have any other option.
Your marriage or...
whatever...
I'll get it done!
Where is my daughter?
- What are you saying?
Didn't you say that she called to remind
you to have medicines even tonight?
Do you think such a person
would leave like this?
She never wished for
us to meet like this.
It was me who ruined all that.
She's not a girl who'd forget the 25
years you raised her, within one night!
You shouldn't be
looking for her here.
Something else has happened.
Shibin, what happened?
- Dude...
I asked at the night shop.
They haven't seen her.
And we checked all the nearby lanes,
and places she could have gone.
She hasn't gone there.
Dude, what about the Church?
No. She hasn't gone
to the Church.
Something serious has happened.
Otherwise she would at
least pick up her phone.
Hello?
- Yes, sir.
We will come there right now.
Okay.
Who is it?
- It's from the station.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Raghavetta...
She has a friend who keeps
calling her regularly.
Shahina.
What if she went there?
Is it?
Who's that?
Son...
Do you know her number?
Don't bother find that.
That was me only.
'Did the flame of life flicker
in an invisible wind?'
'Did the heart skip a beat in anxiety?'
'A star that was hidden
in a snow covered corner'
'Waited for tomorrow's sky'
'There are many long paths ahead'
'Who is here, to guide with directions?'
'The path that can be seen with
the inner eye is the last resort'
'Even when the cold breeze blows through
the veins, someone is standing guard'
'Did the flame of life flicker
in an invisible wind?'
'Did the heart skip a beat in anxiety?'
'A star that was hidden
in a snow covered corner'
'Waited for tomorrow's sky'
Sir, she usually goes to the
Church, after leaving the mall.
But she hasn't gone there today.
So something might have
happened between that.
If we call the cyber cell, won't
we be able to track the location?
That's true!
As if we didn't know that.
No. C.I. Sir is not here.
Call after half an hour.
If things were so easy,
why didn't you go straight to the
cyber cell, without coming here?
I was just asking, sir.
Well, didn't she call you?
You are her lover, right?
What happened?
Had a fight?
When they contacted you earlier,
they didn't get you.
What happened?
I was going to Chennai.
What's in Chennai?
- I got a job there.
You had gone to Chennai,
but how come you're here now?
What did you say your name was?
Azhar.
Sir, he...
Your name is Azhar...
The girl's name is Helen...
You both are in love.
You, who went to Chennai, got a
sudden revelation and came back here.
Taking initiative
for the search.
Totally there seems to be a
spelling mistake, Azhar.
Sir, what are you saying?
What did I do?
Come.
Sir, I spoke to him...
Sit down.
Come.
Let me ask you.
Where is the girl?
- I don't know, sir.
I understood what your plan is.
So if you answer my
questions correctly,
we can all go home peacefully.
Sir, I don't know where she is.
If it's difficult to say
it in front of her dad,
you can tell it to me in secret!
What are you saying, sir?
Or did you sell her to someone?
Mind your words, sir.
Bloody @%@%...
Where's the girl?
I don't know where she is!
Sir, please. He doesn't know.
- Move away!
Can't you see that
I'm questioning him?
Don't think you can play
a damn drama with me!
Troubling me at midnight...
You and your slut of a girl...
Sir!
Didn't he say that he doesn't know?
- Paul!
Don't...
Don't you dare speak ill
about my daughter!
We came to you, because
we don't know anything!
Move!
What is it?
What's the problem?
Sir, he's pouncing on us saying that his
daughter is missing. Bloody... - Hey!
Shut up!
What's the problem?
Sir, it's been 4 hours since
my child went missing.
No investigation has
taken place so far.
Not even a complaint
has been registered.
For suggesting to enquire at cyber cell,
he bashed him up!
Why haven't you
registered the case?
Sir...
How many times have I told you?
Why can't you enquire
at the cyber cell?
Well, sir...
During this midnight...
By the time you fix a time,
if something happens to that girl,
who'd be responsible?
What's the status of her phone?
Sir, it's ringing, but
she isn't picking up.
Go call the cyber
cell and enquire!
Go!
- Okay, sir.
You please come.
Come.
Helen left, sir.
I checked the punch-out list.
Yes.
Then send that list to this number,
immediately.
In this list, it shows that
Helen has punched out.
So, she has left the shop.
But no one has seen her
reaching anywhere.
Did anyone have any problem with her,
or anything like that, recently?
No, sir.
Not to my knowledge.
Sir...
There was a problem with an auto driver,
who used to trouble her.
Auto driver of which stand?
Sir, the stand right
in front of that mall.
Can you identify that driver?
- Yes, sir.
Come.
Sudevan...
- Sir...
Pass this information to
all stations immediately.
And the girl's photo...
You get into the car.
And send the photo of the girl too.
- Yes, sir.
What?
I've sent it, sir.
You should call me as soon
as you get the information.
Okay, sir.
Can you stop the car?
- What happened?
Stop. I'll tell you.
- What?
Dude, stop.
They're stopping the car.
Firo, you can identify
that auto driver, right?
Yes.
- Then get down.
Get into the car with them.
Go.
- What is it, son?
I'll call you.
Dude, what's the matter?
Where is he going?
- Azhar?
Start the car.
Hello!
It's Azhar.
Jins & Amal are staying
somewhere in Girinagar, right?
Yes.
Why?
Send me their numbers right away.
- Why, Azhar?
Sir...
What is it?
- Sir, the phone got switched off now.
I'm not able to pin point
the last location.
You do one thing.
The last tower area, while the
phone got switched off.
Send that.
Okay sir.
I'll send it.
'Did the flame of life flicker
in an invisible wind?'
'Did the heart skip a beat in anxiety?'
'There are many long paths ahead'
'Who is here, to guide with directions?'
Sir, phone!
Sir, it's from the cyber cell.
I'm coming.
What is it?
- It's from the cyber cell.
Must be the girl's location, sir.
It got disconnected.
- Oh no!
Sir, I'm calling from the cyber cell.
That phone got switched
off two minutes back.
So we can't get the
exact location.
The tower area while
it got switched off...
On WhatsApp?
No! No!
I will send it to the C.I.
[an old Malayalam song plays]
Sir, it's him.
What's the matter?
- What is it, sir?
Where's that girl called Helen?
I don't know, sir.
So you don't know
where Helen is?
I don't know, sir.
What is this?
Come here. You'll say it when
we take you to the station.
Sir, he's a fraud, all right.
But he was here all day today.
Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Get his name & details.
Nawaz.
Where is your house?
At Pulleppady...
- There?
It's near the bridge there, sir.
Do you go on night rides?
Yes. On most nights, sir.
Hello?
Hello Ikka?
Where are you?
- I'm coming. Hang up.
Okay.
Chetta...
Hey! Didn't you say
that you left first?
Then how come your
punch-out is after Helen?
Tell me, you rascal.
- Chetta, we left first.
Then? - Only then we
remembered about punching out.
Chetta, that's the truth.
- Where was she then?
Chechi went to keep the stock
into the freezer. - Where?
In the freezer.
- Chetta...
Please.
Who is it?
- It's Ikka. Hello?
Firo, ask them to check the
store's freezer immediately.
Ikka?
Hello?
- Freezer!
What's the matter, Chetta?
Damn it!
Give me your phone. - We didn't take
phones. We came out to buy cigarettes.
What's the matter?
Sir, she has never stayed
over at her friends' places,
without
telling me, so far.
What about the CCTV footage?
Sir, we checked the CCTV footage
of all the nearby shops.
Her face hasn't been
registered in any of it.
What about the mall footage?
Sir, we can't get through
to the mall's manager.
What is this, man?
Everything is like this, huh?
Where does the
mall's manager stay?
Sir, the mall's manager is close by.
A little away from here.
Galaxy apartment.
Come.
You should be here. We'll be right back.
What about the cyber cell?
Any information?
When I called Ratheesh sir,
he said he's checking.
Ask him to make it fast!
- Sir...
Can't you send that tower
location at least now, sir?
C.I. Sir...
and that girl's dad...
put up a great show, right?
Let them be out in the
cold for some time.
It's about a girl's life, sir!
I don't care!
Hey!
Where are you going?
I want to drink some water.
Water is right here.
Won't I give it?
Sit down.
Drink it.
Drink it!
What is it, sir?
- Hey!
What's happening there?
Open it.
- Yes, sir.
Move!
What?
Showing off?
Messing with me?
If you dare to show off
in front of me....
Yes, Sudevan..
- Hello, sir...
Good night.
Hey! Hey!
Slowly! Slowly!
Get up.
Are you okay?
You're bleeding a lot.
I'll take you to the hospital.
No! No!
Are you okay?
You are bleeding.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Please come.
Please.
Raghavetta...
Littu said that, even
after work hours,
she sat there itself, because she didn't
know how to face me, after coming home.
She tried to talk to
me so many times.
If I had spoken to her...
she would have been
with me now, right?
But...
where would my daughter be?
Calm down.
Bhai... Bhai..
You get going.
I'll sit here now.
Okay, brother.
Good night.
Hey! You shouldn't be standing
here in a group like this!
Don't say anything to them.
His daughter has been
missing since night.
Poor guy was crying.
Police came here,
and went to our manager's house.
Okay. You get going.
- Okay, brother.
Hey!
Does that girl work here?
Yes.
At Chicken Hub.
Chicken Hub?
Do you have her photo with you?
Did you enquire at every place
she might go to?
I think that...
this girl hasn't gone
out of the mall.
Sir, the security guard says that she
hasn't gone out from here. - Open it.
Open it, quickly!
Switch on all the lights.
- Okay, sir.
Where is the CCTV room?
'A star that was hidden
in a snow covered corner'
'Waited for tomorrow's sky'
Give me that torch light.
- Dear...
Hasn't the shop's manager reached?
- He said he's on the way, sir.
Ask him to come fast.
Tell him that we'll break it open,
if he doesn't reach quickly.
Did anyone go to check the CCTV?
- Yes, sir.
'Even when the cold breeze blows through
the veins, someone is standing guard'
'Did the flame of life flicker
in an invisible wind?'
'Did the heart skip a beat in anxiety?'
'A star that was hidden
in a snow covered corner'
My dear!!
'Waited for tomorrow's sky'
What is it, sir?
Damn it!
My dear...
'I searched all over the starry sky'
Papa!!
'Tell me, O dear cloud'
Come on!!
'Did the merciful morning
disappear in the starry sky?'
'Did you see my father, whom I
love more than anything in life?'
'O golden star, did you disappear
somewhere in this night?'
'O sky, is the morning ray far away?'
'O golden star, did you disappear
somewhere in this night?'
'O sky, is the morning ray far away?'
'I searched all over the starry sky'
'Tell me, O dear cloud'
My dear...
My dear child...
Dear...
Move!
My darling!
My dear...
Move, I say!
Dear...
My dear...
My daughter is gone, sir!
She's gone, sir!
My dear child...
Papa!
Sir! Sir!
My daughter!
Lift her!
Lift her up, everyone!
Hey! The doctor is here.
There are complications, but...
there's nothing to worry now.
The life-threatening stage is over.
We're lucky that you were able to take
her out, by the time hypothermia struck.
Let her get better. We'll
start physiotherapy.
The scan is here.
- I'll come.
A human cannot stand in a temperature
of 17 degrees in AC, beyond a point.
That's when your daughter...
stayed for 5 hours in there,
at -18 degrees.
I don't know how she survived!
I must say, she's a strong girl.
Don't worry.
Stay strong.
Why can't you keep an alarm?
I don't use alarms usually, sir.
I wake up right on time daily.
It's not about you
setting an alarm.
it's about having an
alarm in the shop.
I was talking about
installing a safety alarm.
Sorry, sir.
I'll get it done.
Sir, they had called
from the cyber cell.
I've got the tower location.
Good!
You loser!
I've told you many times
not to do such shady jobs.
You stay there.
Don't go anywhere. I'm coming...
Sir, it's a hospital.
Hang up!
Sleep!
What's the time. Papa?
Don't worry.
I've given his
'before-food' medicines.
What is this?
A car crashed into my bike.
That's what.
Not that.
Didn't you go to Chennai?
If he had gone,
would he be here now.
Are you both friends now?
Is he someone whom we
can take into our kin, Papa?
I can adjust.
Did you think that I was gone?
No!
I won't go, okay?
I want all of you.
But, for nurses who work here...
salary is very less, I heard.
Right, sister?
We just make do somehow, sir.
We wish that those who're close
to us should be by our side, right?
So...
Let's do that, right?
Here.
Give it, son.
I'll get it.
I'll be right back.
Azhar...
Sit down.
I was going to ask you
to keep an eye on her.
I realized that you would.
I'll be right back.
Wait. Let him come out.
We'll go once Ikka comes.
You wait.
Where did you go, Papa?
- I went to make a call.
Didn't you smoke now, Papa?
- No! No way!
Your hand smells of cigarette.
Hey! I was just...
If you smoke again, I'll tell mom...
- Sir...
How is your daughter?
She opened her eyes. They said
that there's nothing to worry now.
Is it?
That's a relief, right?
Well...
How did you feel that my
child would be in there?
It's been around 30 years
since I started this job.
I see hundreds of people every day.
We've never spoken to
each other till now.
But every day, while
going in and coming out,
your daughter smiles at me,
without fail.
She waves her hand at me.
Yesterday, I got that
while she went in.
But I was sure that I didn't
get that in the evening.
Us, who are noticed by no one...
When someone notices us...
we never forget that
person's face, sir.
Actually, in today's times,
people should be taught
to look at faces & walk,
instead of looking at
the floor & walking.
Okay then.
I am leaving.
It's time for me to
get back to duty.
I can't stay away for too long.
Bye.
I forgot to ask.
What is your
daughter's name, sir?
HELEN